So the answer is a bigger sample. If we chose this one also, and let's say these
所以答案是更大的样本 如果我们也选择这个 那么我们可以说
two, so we double our sample size. Then you see we have this small value 32%.
这两个 所以我们把样本量扩大到两倍 然后你看到我们有这个小的值 32%
And that's going to drag down the sample statistic X bar, the average. So, this
那样会把样本的平均值降低 所以
will be closer to the population average mu. And of course, ideally, we'd want
这样做会更接近总体的均值 当然 理想上 我们想知道
the entire population, but often times that's really hard to do, because the
总体的情况 但通常那样做会很困难 因为
population might be so big. That's when we need a sample. But a bigger sample
总体数量很可能非常大 所以我们需要一个样本 不过更大的样本
will better approximate the population parameter. Another example where samples
能够更好的估计总体参数 另外一个样本
can be misleading is predicting the outcome of the presidential election. For
会产生误差的例子是预测总统选举结果
this last Presidential election with President Obama versus Mitt Romney, a lot
在上次 Obama 对 Mitt Romney 的总统选举中 很多
of polls were given out which each came up with its own result. Some of them
民意测验都会给出它们自己的预测结果 其中一些
predicted that Romney was going to win, which as we know didn't happen. While
认为 Romney 会赢 然而我们知道结果不是这样的 因为
each sample may not perfectly predict population parameters. The sample
每一个样本可能没法完美的预测总体参数 样本
statistic can give us an interval in which the population parameter lies, as
统计量能给我们一个包含总体参数的区间，
long as the sample is random and as unbiased as possible. We'll go more into
只要样本的选取是尽可能随机地、无偏地 之后我们会对样本做
depth about samples later.
更进一步学习